

## Abílio Sérgio Cardoso Fonseca

- +351 91 33 88 597
- 🔀 a.s.cardoso1998@gmail.com
- Largo Diogo Gomes B24 E14 C22, Porto

#### **ABOUT ME**

Experienced Support Technician with 2.3 years in troubleshooting and resolving technical issues across diverse systems. With a strong track record of delivering prompt and effective solutions. Committed to providing exceptional customer service and ensuring seamless technology operations.

#### **EDUCATION**

# Programming and management technician for information systems

Fontes Pereira de Melo School (QNQ level 4) 09/2014 - 07/2017

# Technician specialist in management of networks and informatics systems

ATEC – Academia de Formação (QNQ level 5) 07/2020 – 03/2022

### **EXPERTISE**

SQL Jira Control-M HTML, CSS, JAVASCRIPT Log reading Programming concepts

#### **FAMILIAR**

Linux \ Windows Server
Configuration of routers and switches
Networking protocols
C#, PHP, Python, Nodejs

#### **LANGUAGE**

Portuguese (Native) English

#### **WORK EXPERIENCE**

12/2022 -06/2024 Natixis

#### Applicational Support Specialist

- Resolution and management of tickets via Jira platform
- Investigate issues within the application
- Query Database's in order to check issues with the data
- Log reading in order to fix server jobs using CTM
- Queries development to meet user needs
- Keep communication flowing in crisis situations

03/2022 – 12/2022 Sofyne Active Technology

### Applicational Support Specialist

- Resolution and management of tickets via Jira platform
- Debug application and do fixes on faulty code
- Debug of SQL Queries
- Log reading in order to find issues
- General Windows troubleshoot
- Provide support to the Apriso software users

04/2019 - 06/2020 LÍDER - SERVIÇOS GERAIS DE VIGILÂNCIA, LDA Security Guard

- Provided assistance and information to staff, visitors, and clients, ensuring a safe and welcoming environment while addressing any concerns or inquiries.
- Managed entry and exit points, verified identification, and controlled access to restricted areas to prevent unauthorized entry.